Inventory of the Imre Pozsgay papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Alphabetical file, 1953-1995 and undated (Box 58-88)
  - Aczél, György, 1973-1989 and undated (Folder 58)
    correspondence, reports, newspaper articles
  - Agrártudományi Egyetem, Gödöllő, 1972-1984 and undated (Folder 58)
    correspondence with József Aggod, promotional materials
  - Állami Vagyonügynökség, 1993 and undated (Folder 58)
    reports
  - Antal, László and others, 1984 (Folder 58)
    Az óvatosság kockázata: Tézisek a gazdasági reformpolitikához, a typescript
  - Arrabona University, Győr, 1990-1993 and undated (Folder 58)
    project documents, correspondence, newspaper clippings
  - Ausztráliai Magyar Találkozó, 1994 (Folder 58)
    articles, publications
  - Bács Kiskun Megye administration, 1967, 1987-1993 (Folder 58)
    correspondence, reports, publications
  - Baja synagogue and library, 1985 (Folder 58)
    correspondence, reports, photographs
  - Balassi Bálint Nógrád Megyei Könyvtár, 1988-1989 and undated (Folder 58)
    correspondence, promotional materials, photographs of artworks
  - Balatonfüred, 1991 (Folder 58)
    documents connected with Imre Pozsgay's lecture
  - Balogh, Tibor, undated (Folder 58)
    Merre tart a kecskeméti szinház?, a typescript
  - Báthory, János, 1983 (Folder 58)
    a report on bibliographical sources, primarily on the Western-European politics
  - Belügyminisztérium, 1977-1990 (Folder 58)
  - Berend, Iván T., undated (Folder 58)
    Változások és folytonosságok: a gazdaságpolitika útja Magyarországon 1956-1957 fordulója után, a typescript
  - Bernáth (?), István, undated (Folder 59)
    Északnyugat-európai dosszié, a typescript
  - Bibó, István, undated (Folder 59)
    a series of articles commemorating Bibó, authors:
    - Andrásfalvy, Bertalan, pp. 917-929 (Folder 59)
    - Beke, László, pp. 124-130 (Folder 59)
    - Bence, György and János Kis, pp. 492-516 (Folder 59)
    - Berkovics, György, pp. 54-72 (Folder 59)
    - Bibó, István, pp. 9-35 (Folder 59)
    - Csoóri, Sándor, pp. 96-97 (Folder 59)
    - Csürös, Miklós, pp. 44-53 (Folder 59)
    - Domokos, Mátyás, pp. 517-538 (Folder 59)
    - Duray, Miklós, pp. 98-116 (Folder 59)
    - Éliás, József, pp. 329-347 (Folder 59)
    - Endreffy, Zoltán, pp. 860-877 (Folder 59)
    - Eörsi, István, pp. 376-392 (Folder 59)
    - Erdélyi, Ágnes, pp. 272-282 (Folder 59)
    - Fazekas, László, pp. 372-375 (Folder 59)
    - Fodor, András, pp. 859 (Folder 59)
    - Fügedi, Erik, pp. 967-979 (incomplete) (Folder 59)
    - Granasztói, Pál, pp. 486-491 (Folder 59)
    - Halda, Aliz, pp. 438-443 (Folder 59)
    - Haraszti, Miklós, pp. 829-848 (Folder 59)
    - Illyés, Gyula, pp. 37-38 (Folder 59)
    - Juhász, Pál, pp. 948-969 (Folder 59)
    - Kántor, Lajos, pp. 930-947 (Folder 59)
    - Kenedi, János, pp. 760-809 (Folder 59)
    - Kiss, Csaba, pp. 131-138 (Folder 59)
    - Komlós, Aladár, pp. 42-43 (Folder 59)
    - Kovács, István, 117-123 (Folder 59)
    - Lakatos, István, pp. 355-365 (Folder 59)
    - Litván, György, pp. 156-173 (Folder 59)
    - Márványi, Judit, pp. 295-310 (Folder 59)
    - Mészöly, Miklós, pp. 444-465 (Folder 59)
    - Molnár, Gusztáv, pp. 810-828 (Folder 59)
    - Németh, Lajos, pp. 849-858 (Folder 59)
    - Olitványi, Ambrus, pp. 73-95 (Folder 59)
    - Petri, György, pp. 39-41 (Folder 59)
    - Rácz, Pál, pp. 366-371 (Folder 59)
    - Radnóti, Sándor, pp. 466-485 (Folder 59)
    - Réz, Pál, pp. 539-559 (Folder 59)
    - Szántó, Piroska, pp. 348-354 (Folder 59)
    - Szász, János, pp. 311-328 (Folder 59)
    - Szücs, Jenő, 196-271 (Folder 59)
    - Vajda, Mihály, pp. 745-759 (Folder 59)
    - Varga, Domokos, pp. 422-437 (Folder 59)
    - Vezér, Erzsébet, pp. 283-294 (Folder 59)
  - Bibó, István, 1981, 1989 and undated (Folder 59)
    articles, reports, promotional materials
  - Bihari, Mihály, 1972-1987 and undated (Folder 60)
    typescripts
  - Bolgár Kulturális Központ, 1983-1984 (Folder 60)
    correspondence and articles
  - Borsod-Abaúj-Zemplén Megyei Tanács, 1981 (Folder 60)
    invitations for the celebrations of the 450th anniversary of Rákóczi Gimnázium in Sárospatak
  - Böszörményi, Ernő, Állami Kórház Balatonfüred, 1988-1990 (Folder 60)
    correspondence, András Bajtay, András Veér; documents on cardiology conferences
  - Budapest Főváros XIII. Kerületi Tanácsa, 1984 and undated (Folder 60)
    correspondence on the Raoul Wallenberg monument in Budapest
  - Budapester Rundschau, 1984-1989 (Folder 60)
    correspondence, issues of the newspaper
  - Budapesti Műszaki Egyetem, 1983-1990 (Folder 60)
    correspondence, reports, research papers
  - Csapody, Miklós, undated (Folder 60)
    Az Új Írás 1978/79-es évfolyamáról, a typescript
  - Csath, Magdolna, 1992 (Folder 60)
    correspondence, articles
  - Csoóri, Sándor, 1979-1982 (Folder 60)
    correspondence
  - Deák Ferenc Társaság, undated (Folder 60)
  - Debreceni Nyári Egyetem, 1985 and undated (Folder 60)
    correspondence, program, and audience questions
  - Demokrata Koalíció, undated (Folder 60)
    leaflets
  - A Demokratikus Magyarországért Mozgalom, undated (Folder 60)
    typewritten notes
  - Dialogue as Universal Foundation of Peace, 1986 (Folder 60)
    materials from a conference in Rome; correspondence; papers; reports
  - Domány, András, 1983 (Folder 60)
    reports on political issues in Poland
  - Dubček, Alexander, 1987 (Folder 60)
    an article in typescript, in Hungarian
  - The Economist Intelligence Unit, 1988-1989 (Folder 60)
  - Election campaign and Imre Pozsgay's visit to Israel, 1990 (Folder 60)
    news reports and newspaper clippings
  - Az emberi jogok hazánkban, undated (Folder 61)
    print proofs or photocopies of a book (?)
  - Emigrációs Politikai Főosztály, 1988 (Folder 61)
  - Eötvös Lóránd Tudományegyetem, 1979 and 1988 (Folder 61)
    correspondence and research papers
  - Erdélyi Világszövetség, 1991-1992 (Folder 61)
    correspondence, statutes, promotional materials
  - Erkel Ferenc Énekkar, circa 1985 (Folder 61)
    a photograph
  - Essays on literature and history, undated (Folder 61)
    typescripts; authors-Bagi, Éva and Simon J. Zaven; Bagi, Ibolya; Bernáth, István; Bollók, János; Domokos, Péter; Ferenczi, László; Fried, István; Gergely, András; Gellért, Gyöngyi; Imre, László; Kiss, Csaba; Kocztur, Gizella; Kovács, István; Rákoczi, István; Rozsnyai, Bálint; Sarközi, Péter; Szabó, Kálmán; Szász, Ferenc; Tóth, Éva; Vajda, György; Vásáry, István; and unsigned.
  - EXPO World Exposition, 1990-1991 and undated (Folder 61)
    correspondence, reports, promotional materials
  - Fabrizio, Claude, undated (Folder 62)
    Svéd terv a közművelődés demokratizálására, a typescript
  - Fazekas, János, 1986 and undated (Folder 62)
    correspondence, Ferenc Glatz and Mátyás Szűrös
  - Fekete, Gyula, 1987
    Életszinvonal-alakulás, életszinvonal-koncepció és szocializmus koncepciók Magyarországon, etc., a typescript
  - Fidesz, 1988 and undated (Folder 62)
    reports, promotional materials
  - Finland, a visit of a Hungarian delegation in November 1987, 1973-1987 (Folder 62)
    correspondence, background reports, newspaper articles
  - Finnish-Hungarian cooperation organizations and activities, 1988-1993 and undated (Folder 62)
    correspondence, papers, promotional materials
  - Forgács, Károly, 1981 (Folder 62)
    correspondence, information about him and his project, Köpfe unserer Zeit, photographs
  - Forum Democratique Europeen, 1991 and undated (Folder 62)
    correspondence, conference materials, and reports
  - Free Hungarian Parliament, 1989 (Folder 62)
    correspondence, Erno Hóka, George Bush; promotional materials; a newsletter.
  - A Független Kisgazdászpárt, undated (Folder 62)
    reports, leaflets
  - G+J Textdokumentation, 1987-1989 (Folder 62)
    articles from German and English press on Hungarian issues
  - Gabčíkovo/Bős-Nagymaros Danube dam project, undated (Folder 62)
    reports, articles
  - Gallyas, Ferenc, 1987 (Folder 62)
  - Gáti, Charles, 1983-1988 (Folder 62)
    correspondence, reports, articles
  - Gazdasági Bizottság, 1982, 1985 and undated (Folder 63)
    reports, minutes of meetings
  - Gazdaságirányitási Egyeztető Bizottság, 1982, 1983 and undated (Folder 63)
  - Gorondy-Novák, Sándor, 1988 and undated (Folder 63)
    correspondence, writings, periodicals
  - Grigoly (?), Attila, 1978 (Folder 63)
    A szocialista életmód a nem-anyagi fogyasztás szférájában, a typescript
  - Grósz, Károly, 1953-1958, 1989 and undated (Folder 63)
    correspondence; newspaper articles; archival photocopies of Magyar Dolgozók Pártja and Magyar Szocialista Munkás Párt documents on the 1956 events in Hungary and on Imre Nagy
  - Hazafias Népfront, 1981-1989 and undated (Folder 64-66)
    documents on domestic and foreign affairs, correspondence, speeches, reports, minutes of meetings, publications, promotional materials
    - Hazafias Népfront, 1981-1985 and circa 1981-1985 (Folder 64)
    - Hazafias Népfront, 1985-1987 and circa 1985-1987 (Folder 65)
    - Hazafias Népfront, 1988-1989 and undated (Folder 66)
  - A Hazafias Választási Koalíció, 1990 (Folder 66)
    promotional materials
  - Heuer, Ágnes, 1972 (Folder 66)
    a typescript
  - Honvédelmi Minisztérium, 1969-1992 (Folder 66)
    correspondence, Miklós Németh, Ferenc Kárpáti, István Beregi, others; reports; promotional materials
  - Horvátországi Magyarok Demokratikus Szövetsége, 1995 (Folder 66)
    correspondence, newspaper articles, reports
  - A hoszúperesztegi felső-hegy szabályrendelete, 1984, 1986 and undated (Folder 66)
    reports, newspaper articles, photographs
  - Hubay, Miklós, undated (Folder 66)
    Tüzet viszek: tragédia két részben, a typescript
  - Hunyadi Mátyás Munkaközösség, 1995 (Folder 66)
  - A Hunyadi Szövetség, 1991 and undated (Folder 66)
    correspondence, promotional materials
  - Igazságügyminiszter, 1988 and undated (Folder 67)
  - Illyés, Gyula, undated (Folder 67)
    Egyiptomi világosság, a typescript
  - Illyés Közalapítvány, 1995 and undated (Folder 67)
  - India, organizations, undated (Folder 67)
  - Janics, Kálmán, undated (Folder 67)
    A Hontalanság évei: A szlovákiai magyar kisebbség a második világháború után 1945-1948, a typescript
  - Japan and Japanese-Hungarian cooperation, 1987 and 1990 (Folder 67)
  - József Attila Múzeum, 1981 and undated (Folder 67)
    correspondence, a speech in typescript, a photograph, promotional materials
  - Juhász, György, 1993 and undated (Folder 67)
    correspondence, also László Mravik
  - Kádár, János, 1980-1989 and undated (Folder 67)
    correspondence, speeches, articles, reports
  - Kardos, László, 1979 and undated (Folder 67)
  - Károly, Mihály, undated (Folder 68)
    carbon copies of a letter signed as G. H. and of Károly Mihály válasza, an article in typescript
  - Katholische Akademie Hamburg, 1984-1985 (Folder 68)
    correspondence, itineraries
  - Kekkonen, Urho Kaleva, 1989 and undated (Folder 68)
    a typescript in Hungarian, an article by Imre Pozsgay about Kekkonen's writings, brief notes about Kekkonen
  - Kenedi, János and others, 1980 and 1984 (Folder 68)
    correspondence, István Soltész, Iván Vitányi; reports; an open letter to the readers of Magyar Nemzet
  - Kereskedelmi Minisztérium, 1989 (Folder 68)
    Külgazdasági gyorstájekoztató, a report
  - Kereszténydemokrata Néppárt, 1990 (Folder 68)
  - Kirche Jesu Christi der Heiligen der letzten Tage, 1992 (Folder 68)
  - A kisugó, undated (Folder 68)
  - Kodály, Zoltánné and others, 1981, 1984 and undated (Folder 68)
  - Kodolányi, Gyula, 1987 (Folder 68)
    correspondence, a petition letter
  - Kőhalmy, Tamás, 1988 (Folder 68)
    Magyar Néphadsereg Kaszói Erdő- és Vadgazdaság vadgazdálkodási fejlesztése, a research paper
  - Koltay, Gábor, 1988 (Folder 68)
    correspondence, Imre Pozsgay's review of Ákos Szilágyi's book, Lektori vélemény a Tovább... tovább... tovább! c. kötetről
  - Kommunista Ifjúsági Szövetség, 1983-1988 and undated (Folder 68)
    correspondence, reports, audience questions, publications
  - Könyvvilág, 1984 and undated (Folder 68)
  - KOPINT-DATORG, 1986-1987 (Folder 68)
    correspondence, publications
  - Kósa, Ferenc, 1979 and undated (Folder 68)
    correspondence; A merkőzés, a screenplay in typescript
  - Kozma, Huba, 1984 (Folder 68)
  - Központi Statisztikai Hivatal, 1972-1986 (Folder 69)
    correspondence, articles, publications
  - Közszolgálati Szakszervezetek Szövetsége, 1990 (Folder 69)
    correspondence, a report
  - Kukorelli, István, 1993 and undated (Folder 69)
    writings
  - Külügyminisztérium, 1981-1993 and undated (Folder 69)
    correspondence; reports, including reports from Hungarian embassies abroad; news articles
  - Lahav, Yehuda, 1986 and undated (Folder 70)
    published interviews with Imre Pozsgay; correspondence, Robert László, Pál Szűts
  - Lakitelek meeting in September 1987, circa 1987 and 1991 (Folder 70)
    drafts of Imre Pozsgay's speech; reports, articles, and correspondence on the meeting and on the Lakitelek Alapítvány; speeches by different authors as typescripts
  - László, András, 1975-1991 (Folder 71)
    correspondence, also Gyula Horn, Endre Bócz, Mihály Bihari, István Huszár; reports
  - Levendel, László, 1982-1989 and undated (Folder 71)
    correspondence, also Molnár and Hegedűs; articles and other documents on alcoholism, also Béla Buda and András Veér
  - Lindner, Lutz L., 1992 (Folder 71)
    a letter to Marianne Papp responding on the subject of Support Funding for Eastern Europe and Developing Countries; invoices
  - Lomax, Bill, 1976 (Folder 71)
    1956, a typescript
  - Magyar Atlanti Tanács, 1994 and undated (Folder 71)
  - Magyar Demokrata Fórum, 1989-1995 and undated (Folder 71)
    correspondence, announcements, publications, reports
  - Magyar Egységért Mozgalom, 1995 and undated (Folder 71)
    statutes, promotional materials, forms
  - Magyar Ellenállók, Antifasiszták Szövetsége, 1990 (Folder 71)
    correspondence, a newsletter
  - Magyar Gyógyszerész Kamara, 1993 (Folder 71)
  - Magyar Írók Szövetsége, 1965-1987 (Folder 71)
    minutes of the meeting on 29-30 November 1986; correspondence; reports
  - Magyar Kereskedelmi Kamara, 1984-1987 and 1995 (Folder 71-72)
    correspondence, publications, reports
    - Magyar Kereskedelmi Kamara, 1984-1986 (Folder 71)
    - Magyar Kereskedelmi Kamara, 1987 and 1995 (Folder 72)
  - Magyar Környezetvédelmi Alap, 1988 and undated (Folder 72)
    memoranda and articles on Gabčíkovo/Bős-Nagymaros Danube dam project
  - Magyar Közvéleménykutató Intézet, 1989 (Folder 72)
    reports and publications
  - Magyar Külügyi Intézet, 1987 and 1989 (Folder 72)
  - Magyar Nemzet, 1986 and 1988 (Folder 72)
    correspondence, Dezső Pintér, István Soltész and others
  - Magyar Nemzeti Bank, 1982-1990 (Folder 72)
    correspondence and reports
  - Magyar Nemzeti Kereszténydemokrata Munkáspárt, 1989 (Folder 72)
    correspondence, Miklós Németh
  - Magyar Népfőiskolai Társaság, 1991, 1993 and undated (Folder 72)
  - Magyar Öregdiák Szövetség, 1983-1987 and undated (Folder 72)
    correspondence and promotional materials
  - Magyar Rádió, 1990 (Folder 72)
  - Magyar Szocialista Munkás Párt (MSZMP), 1974-1989 and undated (Folder 72-78)
    documents on domestic and foreign affairs; of different party sub-organizations; correspondence, may contain documents from previous years as attachments; speeches; reports; minutes of meetings; research papers; publications
    - MSZMP, 1974-1978 (Folder 72)
    - MSZMP, 1979-1984 (Folder 73)
    - MSZMP, 1984-1985 (Folder 74)
    - MSZMP, 1986-1987 (Folder 75)
    - MSZMP, 1988-1989 (Folder 76)
    - MSZMP, 1989 (Folder 77)
    - MSZMP, undated (Folder 78)
      undated documents and fragments of documents
  - Magyar Szocialista Párt, 1989-1993 and undated (Folder 78)
    reports, correspondence, promotional materials
  - Magyar Szolidaritási Bizottság, 1984-1985 (Folder 78)
    reports on meetings with Palestinian politicians
  - Magyar-Szovjet Baráti Társaság, 1984-1985 and undated (Folder 78)
    correspondence, reports, other documents
  - Magyar Távirati Iroda, 1983, 1986 and undated (Folder 78)
    correspondence; news reports excerpts
  - Magyar Televízió, 1989 and undated (Folder 78)
  - Magyar Tudományos Akadémia, 1973-1990 and undated (Folder 79)
    correspondence, reports, research papers, publications
  - Magyar Újságírók Szövetsége, 1983 and 1988 (Folder 79)
  - Magyar Vöröskereszt / Hungarian Red Cross, 1993 (Folder 79)
    promotional materials for the Budapesti Tavasz Bál / Spring in Budapest Ball
  - Magyarok: Britain Salutes Hungary arts festival in London, 1989 (Folder 79)
    correspondence, programs, news clippings
  - Magyarok Világszövetsége, 1992-1996 and undated (Folder 79)
  - A Magyarországi egyházak és vallásfelekezetek országos találkozó, 1984 (Folder 80)
    speeches and reports from the meeting on 29 March 1984
  - Magyarországi Németek Demokratikus Szövetsége / Demokratischer Verband der Ungarndeutschen, 1985, 1987 and undated (Folder 80)
    correspondence, publications, newspaper articles, photographs
  - Magyarországi Szociáldemokrata Párt, 1973, 1989 and undated (Folder 80)
    correspondence and publications
  - Minisztertanács, 1978-1990 (Folder 80)
  - Művelődési Minisztérium, 1975-1988 and undated (Folder 80)
    correspondence, articles, reports
  - Nagy, Ernő, 1983 (Folder 80)
    1956: A forradalom sajtója, probably print proofs of a book
  - Németh, László, undated (Folder 81)
    Levél egy kulturpolitikushoz, a typescript
  - Németh László Közép-Európai Népi Akadémia, 1991-1993 and undated (Folder 81)
    correspondence, reports, news articles
  - Nemzeti Demokrata Szövetség, 1991-1995 and undated (Folder 81)
    correspondence, reports, internal documents, promotional materials
  - Nemzetközi Kulturális Intézet, 1988 and 1989 (Folder 81)
  - Népszabadság, 1983-1992 and undated (Folder 82)
    correspondence, articles, other documents
  - Az NSZK-beli út sajtópublikációi a hazai központi napilapokban, 1989 (Folder 82)
    newspaper articles
  - Numismatica Hungarica, György Sóti, 1986, 1989 and undated (Folder 82)
  - Nyiri, Károly, undated (Folder 82)
    A szocialista országok gazdasági fejlodésének a KGST integráció egyes problémáinak hatásai a Magyarországgal való gazdasági kapcsolatok jövojére, a research paper
  - Országgyűlés, 1982-1995 and undated (Folder 82-83)
    reports, correspondence, forms, promotional materials
    - Országgyűlés, 1982-1992 (Folder 82)
    - Országgyűlés, 1992-1995 and undated (Folder 83)
  - Országos Béketanács, 1982-1983, 1987 (Folder 83)
    correspondence, documents on meetings
  - Országos Dohányfüstmentes Egyesület, 1932, 1991-1992 and undated (Folder 83)
    correspondence, articles, anti-smoking campaign materials
  - Országos Műemléki Felügyelőség, 1987 and undated (Folder 83)
    correspondence, reports, and published matter
  - Országos Tervhivatal, 1980 (Folder 83)
  - Országos Tervhivatal, 1980-1987 (Folder 84)
  - Országos Vallásügyi Tanács, 1989 (Folder 84)
    reports, drafts of laws, speeches
  - Páneurópa Unió Egyesülete, undated (Folder 84)
  - Pankovits, József, undated (Folder 84)
    A kultúra helye és szerepe az Olasz Kommunista Párt politikájában 1945-tő napjainkig, a dissertation
  - Pedagógusok Szakszervezete, 1990-1991 (Folder 84)
    correspondence, information on the organization, handwritten notes
  - Pénzügykutatási Intézet, undated (Folder 84)
    Gondolatok gazdasági mechanizmusunk továbbfejlesztésérő, a research paper
  - Pénzügykutató Részvénytársaság, 1989 (Folder 84)
  - Pénzügyminisztérium KISZ Szervezete, 1987 (Folder 84)
    correspondence, activities
  - A politikai intézményrendszer reformja, 1988 and undated (Folder 85)
  - Pozsgai, Joseph, 1990 and undated (Folder 85)
  - Prognózis csoport, 1989 and undated (Folder 85)
    compilation of reports and newspaper articles on Hungarian political organizations and issues, contents:
    - Szabad Demokraták Szövetsége (Folder 85)
    - Bajcsy-Zsilinszky Endre Baráti Társaság (Folder 85)
    - Baloldali Alternativa Egyesülés (Folder 85)
    - Demokratikus Magyarországért Mozgalom (Folder 85)
    - Ellenzéki Kerekasztal (Folder 85)
    - FDSZ (Folder 85)
    - FIDESZ (Folder 85)
    - Független Jogász Fórum (Folder 85)
    - Fügetlen Kiszgazda, Földmunkás és Polgári Párt (Folder 85)
    - FSZDL (Folder 85)
    - Gyermekérdekek Magyarországi Fóruma (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Szociáldemokrata Párt (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Demokrata Fórum Programja (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Demokratikus Ifjúsági Szövetség (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Függetlenségi Párt (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Kereszténydemokrata Párt (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Kereszténydemokrata Néppárt (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Környezetvédelmi Egyesület (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Néppárt (Folder 85)
    - 12+1 pontos kiáltvány (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Realista Népi Mozgalom (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Szociáldemokrata Párt (Folder 85)
    - MSZMP (Folder 85)
    - Munkásszolidaritás '89 (Folder 85)
    - Országos Agrárreformkör (Folder 85)
    - Magyar Demokrata Klub (Folder 85)
    - Prognózis Szakmai Kör (Folder 85)
    - Republikánus Kör (Folder 85)
    - Szabad Demokraták Szövetsége (Folder 85)
    - Szocialista Ifjúsági Szövetség (Folder 85)
    - Szolidaritás Szakszervezeti Munkásszövetség (Folder 85)
    - Társadalmi Igazságtétel Bizottság (Folder 85)
    - Alternatív zöldporgram (Folder 85)
    - Az Új Márciusi Front felhívása (Folder 85)
  - Prognózis Kör, undated (Folder 85)
    economic research papers by Szilvia Borbély, Károly Lóránt, Sándor Nagy, and András Nyilas
  - Radikális Párt, 1989 and 1991 (Folder 85)
  - Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, 1988-1989 (Folder 85)
    situation reports from 16 December 1988, 22 March 1989, and 31 March 1989
  - Rakovski, Marc, 1981 (Folder 86)
    A szovjet típusú társadalom marxista szemmel, a typescript
  - Rakpart Klub, 1989, 1994 and undated (Folder 86)
    minutes, programs, promotional materials
  - Romania, Hungarian minority issues, 1988, 1995 and undated (Folder 86)
    domestic and international activities
  - Romániai Magyarok Demokratikus Szövetsége, 1991 (Folder 86)
    a report by Csaba Tabajdi
  - Rosati, Domenico, 1986 (Folder 86)
    correspondence, newspaper articles
  - Rossy, Vilmos, 1938 and undated (Folder 86)
    photocopies of letters by Rossy and others, a handwritten note by Rossy
  - Salgo, Nicolas M., 1984-1985 (Folder 86)
    correspondence and an interview
  - Schöpflin, George, 1978 (Folder 86)
    A romániai magyarság / The Hungarians of Rumania. Minority Rights Group, Report No. 37. London, 1978 (in Hungarian)
  - Second Vienna Dialogue International Conference-Dialogue for Disarmament and Détente, 1983 (Folder 86)
    correspondence, reports, activities
  - Somfai, András, Győriterv, 1988 (Folder 86)
    research papers
  - Sopron Gimnázium, 1982 and undated (Folder 86)
    documents connected with organizing of the school's 425th founding anniversary
  - Szabad Demokraták Szövetsége, 1988-1990 and undated (Folder 86)
    newspaper articles, periodicals and promotional materials
  - Szabó, Miklós, undated (Folder 86)
    Magyar nemzettudat problémák a 20. sz. második felében, an article
  - Szakszervezetek, 1980-1987 and undated (Folder 86)
    correspondence, speeches, reports
  - Szegő, Andrea, 1991, 1993 and undated (Folder 87)
  - Szent György Lovagrend, 1994 and 1995 (Folder 87)
  - Szűrös, Mátyás, 1982-1990 (Folder 87)
    correspondence, reports, interviews
  - Tarnói, László, 1989-1990 and undated (Folder 87)
  - Társadalmi Szemle, 1974-1990 and undated (Folder 87)
    correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings
  - Teleki László Alapítvány, 1992 (Folder 87)
  - Tiszadob, Andrássy kastély, undated (Folder 87)
    reports, a photograph of the castle
  - Thürmer, Gyula, 1993 (Folder 87)
    speeches, reports